privacydr.com 2018-01-02

# 

Privacy Policy 

PrivacyDr is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to PrivacyDr. 

Information Collection 

When you purchase, download trial or evaluation versions, or register PrivacyDr Software, we may collect personal information including your name, address, email address, etc. for the purpose of recording the transaction when you engage in activities on our web site or within the PrivacyDr software. When we use a payment processing merchant we ensure that the same strict privacy criteria are in place. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. We also give users the option of receiving useful product information (such as updates, pest alerts and associated product offerings), via opt-in permission based email. We fully ensure your privacy and value your trust. We will never sell, rent, lease or trade your personal information to any third party. Likewise, your information will not be shared with a third party in any other way unless PrivacyDr is required to do so by law. PrivacyDr may engage the services of a third party from time to time and may provide certain information that includes personal information in order for the third party to perform such services. Any third parties who provide services to PrivacyDr have agreed not to disclose your information or use it for any other purpose, and are required to implement or adopt a Privacy Policy that is no less stringent than PrivacyDr Privacy Policy. You may opt out of receiving emails from us at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email. By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to PrivacyDr collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein. 

Any information that you post to a chat room, public bulletin or forum is available to all users of that site. PrivacyDr cannot control, nor is it responsible for the use, disclosure, or dissemination of such information by any third parties. 

Web Site Usage 

We may automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information when you access our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors navigate our sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors, length of visits, etc. 

How Information Is Used When Collected 

We may use information collected in the following ways: 

â€¢ To process, validate and verify purchases. 

â€¢ To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of information provided. 

â€¢ To register you as a customer. 

â€¢ To open and maintain a support account for you. 

â€¢ To send email notifications about new, existing, enhanced products or services. 

â€¢ To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide added products and services. 

â€¢ To enable us to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations. 

â€¢ To provide advance notice of termination of a trial period or an opportunity to extend a trial period, or advance notice of expiration of your software license. 

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights), and your compliance with the applicable End User License Agreement(s) contained within the PrivacyDr Software. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the applicable law may require us to do so. 

Cookies 

We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our services. PrivacyDr employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to our customers or to our affiliates and/or other sales partners, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All PrivacyDr cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to PrivacyDr , and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information. Our Cookies are mainly maintained to track our affiliates and/or other sales partners to ensure proper payments for their sales and tracking activities relating to their affiliate relationship with us. 

Links 

We may offer links from our website and software to other third party websites which may be hosted by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and PrivacyDr makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit. 

Policy Modifications 

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you in order to reflect our practices and provide greater protection for your information. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted promptly here, so please check back periodically. 

Acceptance of Terms 

By using the PrivacyDr services, accessing the PrivacyDr web site and/or PrivacyDr software sites, or purchasing PrivacyDr products you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this Privacy Policy. 

Operated by EuroTrade A.L Ltd   
+1(855)7343597
